John M Berry

102 Cedar St Glasgow, KY 42141 270-834-9080 | johnb@bluegrassitc.com www.linkedin.com/in/john-berry-175b4914

Summary

Very technical IT Support Technician has terrific troubleshooting and good interpersonal skills to assist customers with computer issues. Possesses a thorough knowledge of computer and network hardware, operating systems and software applications. 24 years of experience working as an IT Support Technician. Additionally, currently a student at BC Skills looking to further my career with this class of Web Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ultratech Computer Services / Bluegrass IT & Computer Services, Glasgow, KY October 1997 - Present

- · Ability to configure Windows desktop computers under common scenarios.
- · Adhering to wiring standards and using test tools.
- Configuring hardware, applications and network connectivity.
- Entry-level server management, configureation and support including coverage of Active Directory and Network
 Infrastructure, as well as Maintain, Troubleshoot, Install, Operate and Configure Basic Network hardware.
- Experience supporting Windows Operating Systems and application installation and support.
- PC Repair and Support including Virus removal.
- Possess good soft skills to work with clients in a user-friendly, non-technical language.
- Strong general troubleshooting methods and abilities.
- Peripheral installation, maintenance and troubleshooting.
- Excellent internet search skills to find answers when troubleshooting issues not seen before.

Dunlap Sales, Glasgow, KY

June 1977 - September 1997

Asst Manager

- · Troubleshooting and repair of Industrial Electronic Control Systems.
- Created and maintained computerized inventory control database.
- Maintained Office Computers and Networking.

EDUCATION

WKU, Bowling Green August 1974 - Dec 1976

Computer Science - Programming languages: BASIC, IBM Assembly Language, FORTRAN

REFERENCES

Barry Harlow - Mgr. Dunlap Sales

Bernard Williams - Owner Oliver Williams & Co.

Barry Coffey - Owner Glasgow Filter Products

AWARDS / VOLUNTEERING / INTERESTS

Junior Scholars Program, WKU

Summer 1973 6-hrs college credit summer between Jr & Sr Year of High School

Who's Who Among American High School Students 1973-1974

Photography - associate member of KPPA 1975-1978

Glasgow Highland Games Board of Directors - 1986 - Present